Lauren Dubin 2835 WEBB AVENUE APT. 8G BRONX, NY 10468

CELL: 917-392-2569 PHONE/FAX (718) 549-3568 laurendbrnx2005@aol.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A skilled and dedicated Administrative, Data Entry, and Customer Service professional with 10 years experience coordinating, planning, and supporting daily operational functions. Excellent written and oral communication skills. Experience handling sensitive and confidential business. Superior organizational and multi-tasking skills. Ability to work independently with minimal supervision, as well as in team environment. Highly motivated individual with professional demeanor.

SKILLS

Data Entry, Typing (80+ WPM), Transcription, Medical Scribe, fast long-hand, familiarity with ICD-10 medical coding, insurance, pre-certifications/authorizations, Windows 10, Microsoft Office 365 which includes Word 2019, Excel 2019, PowerPoint 2019, Access 2019, Outlook, and Publisher, Eudora, EPIC, NextGen, Athena, Mozilla Firefox & Thunderbird, Adobe applications, Mac computers, electronic tablets, QuarkXPress, PC DOCS, medical terminology, Electronic Medical Records, most transcription systems including internet applications, and voice recognition software such as PowerScribe, Legal word processing centers, reception including Call Centers, clerical, scanning, data entry, customer service, computer tech support/Help Desk (problem solving & troubleshooting abilities), maintaining filing and database systems.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Metropolitan Transportation Authority Bronx, NY

August 2017-PRESENT

Data Entry/Office assistant

- Comparing data entered with source documents.
- Correcting errors when appropriate.
- Maintaining required records of all completed work and compiling weekly reports.
- Assist in maintaining filing system by organizing, purging, maintaining and retrieving files.
- Clerical duties as assigned

Acacia Network, Bronx, NY Medical Scribe

December 2016 - June 2017

- Anticipate physician needs to facilitate the flow of clinics.
- Accurately and thoroughly record patient medical history and physical exam, procedures and treatments performed by healthcare professionals, including nurses and physician assistants.
- Patient education and explanations of risks and benefits, physician-dictated diagnoses, prescriptions and instructions for patient or family members for self-care and follow-up.
- Prepare referral letters as directed by the physician.
- Collect, organize and catalog data for physician quality reporting system and other quality improvement efforts and format for submission.
- Attend trainings on diverse subjects such as information technology, legal, HIPAA and regulatory compliance, billing and coding. Quickly assimilate new knowledge into process and procedures.
- Proofread and edit all the physician's medical documents for accuracy, spelling, punctuation and grammar.
- Utilizing NextGen Electronic Medical Record system.
- Use of Microsoft Word 2016, Outlook 2016

Tunstall Medical Alert - Long Island, NY

March 2016 - July 2016

Data Entry Operator, Customer Service Representative | Temporary Assignment

- Entering alphanumeric information into computer system in preparation for medical billing
- Assisting with authorizations for installation of medical alert equipment
- Electronic and paper filing

- Customer service duties
- Clerical duties as assigned

Mill Basin Radiology Services – New York, NY

October 2013 - November 2017

Remote Medical Transcriptionist/Medical data entry |Part-time and Per Diem)

- Home based transcription utilizing Word 2013 of time sensitive material in formatted medical radiology reports, mainly sonograms on an as needed basis, often with deadlines
- Entry of medical data in radiology and medical procedures into Microsoft Word
- Use of Windows 10, medical terminology, Office 2013 including Outlook

Patient Care Associates - Mamaroneck, NY

November 2012 - June 2013

Medical Data Entry Operator and Transcriptionist, Office Assistant

- Entering of medical data of radiology and cardiology formats for acute care facilities involving deadlines and time sensitive material, record keeping of same, projects and spreadsheets recording productivity
- Use of medical terminology, internet incorporated transcription and dictaphone applications
- Reception and clerical support as needed

Mill Basin Radiology Services – New York, NY Senior In-House Medical Transcriptionist, Secretary

November 2011 – October 2012

- Entry of medical data in radiology and medical procedures into Microsoft Word 2003, often with deadlines, time sensitive material formatted into medical radiology reports, mainly sonograms
- Filing
- Record keeping
- Problem solving and troubleshooting
- Reception and clerical support as needed
- Use of medical terminology, Windows XP, Microsoft Word 2003 and Excel 2003

Weill Cornell Medical College – New York, NY Medical Administrative Assistant

May 2009 - September 2011

- Performed administrative support services for the Director and Faculty of the Myeloproliferative Diseases program in the Department of Medicine/ Division of Hematology and Medical Oncology. Maintained computerized calendar
- Coordinated scheduling appointment process for long-term scheduling monthly, weekly, and daily views
- Coordinated all necessary paperwork for daily meetings and events
- Dealt with press and broadcast media to set up arrangements for the Director's public appearances
- Handled travel arrangements including local, domestic, and foreign travel
- Handled confidential information and situations on a daily basis
- Screened all phone calls
- Assisted in preparation and typing of research grants and contract applications and protocol submissions
- Data entry of clinical material as dictated into Epic electronic medical record
- Performed other job-related duties as required. Use of medical terminology, Windows XP, Microsoft Office 2007, Eudora, Mozilla Firefox & Thunderbird, Adobe, Outlook, and Epic

JCW Enterprises Typing Service – New York, NY Remote Medical Transcriptionist

November 2005 - December 2010

- Home based typing and transcription, work was on a contract basis and commission and consisted of medical transcription and data entry of radiology and surgical reports
- Use of Windows XP, Microsoft Office 2003: Word and Excel, Centricity and internet applications; RTAS dictaphone

EDUCATION

The Rhodes School – New York, NY High School Diploma

Mandl School – The College of Allied Health – New York, NY
Medical Secretary Science Certificate